by RentAnAdviser.com
Take take it easy word to 94
I got twenty four hours,
twenty four hours
Twenty four ***s in the hotel tower
Twenty four ******* on
the guest list yeah
Twenty four carats on
my necklace yeah
Twenty four hours twenty four hours
Twenty four ***s in the hotel tower
Twenty four ******* on
the guest list yeah
Twenty four carats on
my necklace yeah
Ballin like I am Kobe Swish,
2 4 on my jersey
I stay with the homies they
pop out if you hurt me
I might cop a Rollie for all
the ***s who curved me
When I pull up swervin′ that′s
that Lamborghini Mercy
I might do the dash goin fast
in the coupe In the coupe
I have been gettin cash all my racks
lookin blue Lookin blue
Chains gon splash when
I smash in the pool
Yeah I don′t take no nap,
I be stackin two to two
I am mixin with the cup she just
put somethin in my water
Three shots ain′t enough my
shorty pour me up stronger
We just got the addy
and she on one too
We pull up with baddies
to the hotel room
I got twenty four hours,
twenty four hours
Twenty four ***s in the hotel tower
Twenty four ******* on the guest
list yeah Guest list yeah
Twenty four carats on my necklace,
yeah Necklace yeah
Twenty four hours twenty four hours
Twenty four ***s in the hotel tower
Twenty four ******* on the guest
list yeah Guest list yeah
Twenty four carats on my necklace,
yeah Necklace yeah
Twenty four hours twenty four hours
Twenty four hours twenty
four hours yeah
by RentAnAdviser.com